After exploring the day and night image data,
浏览白天和夜间的图像数据后
you may have noticed a part of the data that we haven't yet gone over,
你可能注意到 有部分数据我们还没有讨论
a label associated with each image.
每个图像都关联了一个标签
So what exactly is a label and why do we need it?
标签到底是什么 为什么需要标签？
A label is kind of like a tag that's attached to
标签有点像一个标记 附加到
a specific image and that tells you something about that image.
具体图像 提供该图像的一些信息
You can think of a label sort of like a name tag.
你可以把标签看作胸牌
I wear a name tag to events when I meet new people and my name tag labels me as Cezanne.
比如 我参加活动 和陌生人见面时 我会戴一个胸牌 我的胸牌告诉别人 我叫 Cezanne
Now, an image can have multiple labels that describe it,
图像可能有多个标签
which would be like if I had multiple labels like "human"
比如 我可以有多个标签 包括 “人类”
or "wears glasses" that each described something about me.
“戴眼镜” 等等 每个标签提供了我的部分信息
But for this lesson, we'll be working with one label per image.
但在本课中 我们只考虑一副图像一个标签的情况
These labels separate the image data into classes,
这些标签把图像数据分为不同的类
and classes are like general categories.
类就是简单的分组
So the label for me might be human,
因此 我的标签可能是人类
which is a category distinct from a label like a table or a car or any other thing,
这个分组和其他标签有明显区分 如桌子、汽车或其他东西的标签
and it's more general than a label like Cezanne.
而且也比 Cezanne 这个标签更泛化
So for the image datasets we work with,
因此 对于我们用到的图像数据集
we should have as many labels as we have classes.
我们的标签数量应该和类的数量一样
In the case of our day and night images,
在白天和夜间图像的例子中
we have two labels, day and night.
我们有两个标签 白天和夜间
Now, why do we need these labels?
那么 我们为什么需要这些标签呢
You can tell if an image is night or day but
你可以区分图像是白天还是夜间
a computer cannot unless we tell it explicitly with a label.
但是电脑无法区分 所以我们要通过标签明确告诉电脑
This becomes especially important when we're testing
当我们测试分类模型准确度时
the accuracy of a classification model.
这非常重要
A classifier takes in an image as input and should output
分类器读入一副图像 并且应该输出
a predicted label that tells us the predicted class of that image.
一个预测标签 告诉我们预测的图像类
Now, when we load in data like you've seen,
然后 当我们载入你看到的数据时
we load in what are called the true labels,
我们载入的是真实的标签
and the true label is just the correct label for that image.
这个真实标签就是这幅图像的正确标签
To check the accuracy of our classifier,
要检查分类器的准确度
we compare the predicted and true labels.
我们要对比预测标签和真实标签
If the true and predicted labels match,
如果两者吻合
then we've classified the image correctly.
那么我们对图像的分类就是正确的
But sometimes, the labels do not match,
但有时候 标签并不吻合
which means we've misclassified an image.
也就是说 我们的图像分类是错误的
After looking at many, many images,
在观察了大量图像后
the accuracy of a classifier is defined as the number of correctly classified images,
分类器的准确度可以定义为 正确识别的图像数量所占的比例
for which the predicted label matches the true label,
即预测标签和真实标签吻合的图像数量
divided by the total number of images.
除以总图像数量
So say we tried to classify 100 total images and we correctly classified 81 of them,
假设我们尝试对 100 幅图像进行分类 其中 81 幅图像分类正确
meaning we misclassified 19 of them.
也就是说 19 幅分类错误
That would mean we'd have 0.81 or 81 percent accuracy.
那么准确率就是 0.81 或 81%
And we can only tell a computer to check the accuracy of
要让计算机检查分类器的准确率
a classifier when we have these predicted and true labels to compare.
我们必须有这些预测标签和真实标签可以对比
We can also learn from any mistakes
我们还可以从分类器的错误中学习
the classifier makes as we'll see later in this lesson.
在本课后面部分我们再讨论
As a note, it's good practice to use
提示一下 使用数字标签比
numerical labels instead of strings or categorical labels.
使用字符串或类别标签更好
Numbers are easier to track and compare.
数字更容易追踪对比
So for our day and night binary class example,
因此 对于上面的白天和夜间二进制类
instead of day and night labels,
我们不使用白天和夜间标签
we'll use the numerical labels zero for night and one for day.
而使用数字标签 0 表示夜间 1 表示白天
Okay. Now you're familiar with
好的 现在 你已经熟悉了
the day and night image data and you know what a label is and why we use them.
白天和夜间的图像数据 知道了标签是什么 以及为什么使用标签
You're ready for the next steps.
接下来 我们学习后续步骤
We'll be building a classification pipeline from start to end.
我们会从头到位构建一个分类流程
Let's first brainstorm what steps we'll take to classify these images.
首先 我们头脑风暴一下 要分类这些图像需要哪些步骤